<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Panthers Baseball &amp; Softball</string>
    <string name="title_home">Information</string>
    <string name="title_news">News</string>
    <string name="title_book">Fixtures &amp; Results</string>
    <string name="title_contact">Contact</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="long_Text">

        This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This
        This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This This

        IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS
        IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS IS

        The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The
        The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The The

        Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last
        Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last Last

        Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment
        Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment Fragment


    </string>

    <string name="about">
        Far curiosity incommode now led smallness allowance. Favour bed assure son things yet.
        She consisted consulted elsewhere happiness disposing household any old the. Widow downs you new shade drift hopes small.
        So otherwise commanded sweetness we improving. Instantly by daughters resembled unwilling principle so middleton.
        Fail most room even gone her end like. Comparison dissimilar unpleasant six compliment two unpleasing any add.
        Ashamed my company thought wishing colonel it prevent he in. Pretended residence are something far engrossed old off.

    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
